Finding Aid for Michigan Interscholastic Forensic Association records
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Administration 1934-2006
  - Mailings
    - Bound Materials (Debate, Novice, J.S. Knight) 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Bound (Debate-Miscellaneous) 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Bound Materials (Student Congress, Discussion, One-Act Plays) 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Bound Materials (Miscellaneous) 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Bound Materials (Winning Orations) 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Bound Materials (Mailing Lists, District Events) 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - 1968-1972 (Box 11)
    - 1972-1973, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - 1974-1977 (Box 11)
    - 1977-1980 (Box 11)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 11)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 12)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 12)
    - 1983-1984, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - 1987-1988, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - 1988-1990 (Box 12)
    - 1990-1993 (Box 12)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 12)
    - 1996-1997, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 13)
    - 2000-2002 (Box 13)
    - 2002-2003 (Box 13)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 13)
    - 2004-2005 (Box 13)
  - Topical
    - Adrian College (Box 13)
    - Albion College (Box 13)
    - Alma College (Box 13)
    - Annual Reports (Box 13)
    - Aquinas College (Box 13)
    - Authorization Issues (Box 13)
    - Awards, 3 folders (Box 13)
    - Ballot Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Bay De Noc Community College (Box 13)
    - Brochures/Handbooks -- Correspondence, Drafts (Box 13)
    - Bureau of School Services (University of Michigan) -- Correspondence, Reports (Box 13)
    - Calvin College (Box 13)
    - Central Michigan College (Box 13)
    - Chrysler Institute (Box 13)
    - Classification Issues (Box 13)
    - Committee -- Future MIFA (Box 13)
    - Committee -- Revolving (New Sources for Readings) (Box 13)
    - Committee -- Transition (Box 13)
    - Committees -- Standing (Compositions) (Box 13)
    - Conferences/Retreats (Box 13)
    - Correspondence -- General, 7 folders (Box 13)
    - Correspondence -- General, 5 folders (Box 14)
    - Correspondence -- Newsletter Articles, Publications (Box 14)
    - Correspondence -- Requests for Materials (Box 14)
    - Detroit News -- Correspondence, Invoices for Awards (Box 14)
    - Detroit Public Schools (Box 14)
    - East Texas State University (Box 14)
    - Eastern Michigan College (Box 14)
    - Eligibility Rulings (Box 14)
    - Events Summaries (Box 14)
    - Ferris Institute (Box 14)
    - Bound Materials -- Financial Statements (1950-1968) (Box 14)
    - Financial Statements (Box 14)
    - Financial -- Budget Summaries (Box 14)
    - Financial -- Budget Summaries for Specific Activities (Box 14)
    - Financial -- Fees Increases, Budget Projections (Box 14)
    - Financial -- Self-Sufficiency, University Accounts (Box 14)
    - Financial -- Tax Exempt/Nonprofit Status, Grant, Endowment Plan (Box 14)
    - Fiscal Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Flint Junior College (Box 14)
    - Flint University of Michigan Branch (Box 14)
    - Forensic Council -- At-Large Ballots (Box 14)
    - Forensic Council -- Candidate Biographies (Box 14)
    - Forensic Council -- Constitutions (Box 14)
    - Forensic Council -- Correspondence from State Manager (Box 14)
    - Forensic Council -- Member Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Forensic Council -- Job Description, Recognition of Members (Box 14)
    - Forensic Council -- Membership Lists (Box 14)
    - Forms -- Enrollment Cards, Debate and Forensic Ballots (Box 14)
    - Forms -- Hosting of Activities (Box 14)
    - Forms and Form Letters -- Assorted (Box 14)
    - General Forensic Questionnaires/Other Surveys, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Hillsdale College (Box 14)
    - History -- various materials (Box 14)
    - History-"A Study of the History, Administration, and Techniques of the Michigan High School Forensic Association Contests." L.W. Grosser 1948 (Box 14)
    - History Drafts, Manuscripts of James Irwin 1967 (Box 14)
    - Bound volume, "The Michigan High School Forensic Association" James R. Irwin 1968 (Box 14)
    - General Motors Institute (Box 14)
    - Grand Rapids Junior College (Box 14)
    - Hope College (Box 14)
    - Judge Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Kellogg Community College (Box 14)
    - Lake Superior State College (Box 14)
    - Lists -- Directors of Debate or Forensics (Box 14)
    - Lists -- Events Calendars (Box 14)
    - Lists -- Judges for Various Events (Box 14)
    - Lists -- Tournaments and Workshops (Box 14)
    - Mailing Lists Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Membership -- Contact of Delinquent Programs (Box 14)
    - Membership Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Michigan Association of School Administrators (Box 15)
    - Michigan Association of Secondary School Principals, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Michigan Colleges and Universities (Box 15)
    - Michigan Lung Association (Box 15)
    - Michigan Speakers Bureau (Box 15)
    - Michigan Speech Association (Box 15)
    - Michigan Speech Coaches Association, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Michigan State University (Box 15)
    - Mid-Michigan College (Box 15)
    - National Federation of State High School Associations, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - National Forensic League (Box 15)
    - National University Extension Association, 8 folders (Box 15)
    - North Central Michigan College (Box 15)
    - Northern Michigan College (Box 15)
    - Northwestern Michigan College (Box 15)
    - Notable Michiganders -- Involvement in Forensic Activities (Box 15)
    - Oakland University (Box 15)
    - Orders for Manuals (Box 15)
    - Policies -- Assorted (Box 15)
    - Policies -- Ethics (Box 15)
    - Policies -- Fiscal (Box 15)
    - Policies -- Regionalization (Box 15)
    - Policies -- Sexual Harassment (Box 15)
    - Policies -- Title IX Compliance (Box 15)
    - Relocations of Offices (Box 15)
    - Reports (Assorted)/Summaries/Promotional Items (Box 15)
    - Resolutions/Remembrances (Box 15)
    - School Membership Lists, 9 folders
      - Middle School Membership Lists (Box 15)
    - Secretary's Manual, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Secretary/Office Assistant Position (Box 15)
    - Special Communiques-1967 (Box 15)
    - State Manager/Executive Director Duties; Fitzgerald Hiring (Box 15)
    - Suomi College (Box 15)
    - Television Program (Box 15)
    - Topical Studies -- Assorted (Box 15)
    - Transcript -- Radio Broadcast (Box 15)
    - University of Detroit (Box 15)
    - University of Michigan (Box 16)
    - Upper Peninsula High School Forensic Association, 4 folders (Box 16)
    - Upper Peninsula -- Ironwood Request (Box 16)
    - Wayne University (Box 16)
    - Website Development and Usage/Other Computer and Database Issues (Box 16)
    - Western Michigan University (Box 16)
    - Workshops, 7 folders (Box 16)
- Publications 1928-2007
  The Publications series contains various types of compiled information produced by MIFA. This series contains bulletins of the Michigan High School Debating League, 1917-1932/33, detailing information about this direct predecessor of MIFA. There are annual issues of Speech Activities, 1951/52-2000, which detail the rules and regulations for MIFA activities. Also found in this series is a comprehensive set of the organization's newsletter, mostly under the title of Forensic News, for the period 1928/29-1997. These newsletters would be a useful place to begin to obtain a general understanding of MIFA functions and how the organization has operated. They provide useful insight regarding the transition to the MHSFA in 1933 as well as information about contests. In addition, this series contains programs from various John S. Knight and state debate contests, as well as from state drama/theatre events and Youth Arts Festivals. Anniversary programs and booklets, providing summary and historical information for selected activities, are also included as are manuals and posters.
  - Drama/Theatre Materials
    - Michigan Youth Arts Festival Programs 1975-2006 (Box 16)
    - Michigan Youth Arts Festival Creative Writing Certificate of Merit Award Winners 1997, 1999, 2002, 2003 (Box 16)
    - Michigan Youth Arts Festival -- Brochures, Histories (folder) (Box 16)
    - Michigan High School Drama Competition -- Perspective of the First Ten Years 1979/80 (folder) (Box 16)
    - Programs -- State Drama Finals 1970/71-1990/91 (folder) (Box 16)
    - Programs -- State Theatre Festivals 1991/92-2006/07 (folder) (Box 16)
  - Debate Materials
    - Debate Handbooks 1972, 1976 (folder) (Box 17)
    - Poster Announcing Detroit Free Press Debate Scholarship 1948 (folder) (Box 17)
    - Programs -- John S. Knight Scholarship Contests in Debate 1948-2004 (folder) (Box 17)
    - 50th Anniversary Booklet of the John S. Knight Scholarship Contest 1997 (folder) (Box 17)
    - Debate Awards -- Brochure and Posters 1935/36-1952/53 (folder) (Box 17)
    - Debate Awards and Scholarships -- Booklets and Brochures 1962/63-1992/93 (folder) (Box 17)
    - State Championship Debate Posters 1937-1962 (folder) (Box 17)
    - Debate Posters 1957/58-1962/63 (Box 17)
    - State Championship Debate Programs 1926-2004, 5 folders (Box 17)
    - 75th Anniversary Booklet of Debate in Michigan High Schools 1991 (folder) (Box 17)
    - NUEA Debate Handbooks 1942/43-1943/44 (Box 17)
    - NUEA Discussion and Debate Manuals, September, 1952-1963/64 (Box 17)
    - MIFA Discussion and Debate Booklets, 1951/52- circa 1970 (Box 17)
    - Booklet -- Affirmative and Negative Debate Briefs on the 1964-65 Michigan High School Debate Question (Box 17)
    - Booklet -- Judicial Reform: The Jury System for the 1970s (Analysis for the 1971-72 High School Debate Topic) (Box 17)
  - Individual Events Materials
    - Supplement to the 1934-35 Collection of Public Speeches for Declamation 1935 (Box 18)
    - Public Speeches for Declamation, Series Three 1936 (Box 18)
    - Forensic Posters -- Dictionary Awards 1945/46-1951/52 (folder) (Box 18)
    - Forensics Handbooks 1972 (folder) (Box 18)
    - 1996-1997 Individual Events Series Booklet; Awards and Scholarships Brochures (folder) (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Assorted Brochures (folder) (Box 18)
  - Bulletins
    - Michigan High School Debating League, 1917-1932/33 (folder) (Box 18)
    - Michigan High School Forensic Association 1933/34-1950/51, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - Speech Activities
    (all bound unless otherwise noted)
    - Spring 1951-1952 (Box 18)
    - Lower Peninsula, Spring 1953 (Box 18)
    - Upper Peninsula, Spring 1953 (Box 18)
    - Lower Peninsula, Spring 1954 (Box 18)
    - Upper Peninsula, Spring 1954 (Box 18)
    - Lower Peninsula, Spring 1955 (Box 18)
    - Upper Peninsula, Spring 1955 (Box 18)
    - Lower Peninsula, Spring 1956 (Box 18)
    - Upper Peninsula, Spring 1956 (Box 18)
    - Lower Peninsula, Spring 1957 (Box 18)
    - Upper Peninsula, Spring 1957 (Box 18)
    - Spring 1958 (Box 18)
    - Spring 1959 (Box 18)
    - Spring 1960 (Box 18)
    - Spring 1961 (Box 18)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 18)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 18)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 18)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 18)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 18)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 18)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 18)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 18)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 18)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 18)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 18)
    - 1979-1980 (Box 18)
    - 1980-1981 (folder) (Box 18)
    - 1981-1982 (folder) (Box 18)
    - 1982-1983 (Box 18)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 18)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 18)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 18)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 18)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 18)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 18)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 18)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 18)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 18)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 18)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 18)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 18)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 18)
    - Summaries of Revisions 1976/77-2000/01 (folder) (Box 18)
    - Revisions to Debate Activities 2001/02-2005/06 (folder) (Box 18)
    - Revisions to Individual Events Activities 2004/05-2006/07 (folder) (Box 18)
    - Revisions to Theatre Activities 2003/04-2004/05 (folder) (Box 18)
  - Newsletters
    a(ll bound unless otherwise noted)
    - 1928/29-1932/33 (Box 19)
    - 1933/34-1937/38 (Box 19)
    - 1938/39-1942/43 (Box 19)
    - 1943/44-1948/49 (Forensic News) (Box 19)
    - 1949/50-1955/56 (Box 19)
    - 1956/57-1959/60 (Box 19)
    - 1960/61-1962/63 (Box 19)
    - 1963/64-1964/65 (Box 19)
    - 1965/66-1966/67 (Box 19)
    - Individual Issues September, 1967-Fall 1978 (Box 19)
    - Scattered issues 1983-1997 (unbound folder) (Box 19)
- Photographs 1918-1997
  The Photographs series includes photographs, negatives, and contact sheets of various state contests. This series also contains photos of many debaters and coaches throughout the years, along with photographs of some of the State Managers of MIFA.
  - Debaters, Coaches, and Teams 1918-1953, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Debaters 1956-1964, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Debaters, Coaches, and Teams circa 1960-1964 (Box 20)
  - State Debate 1965-1970, 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Debate Teams circa 1976 (Box 20)
  - State Debate 1977-1996, 9 folders (Box 20)
  - Debaters 1992-1999 (Box 20)
  - Debate Coaches circa 1948-1964 (Box 20)
  - Michigan High School Forensic Association Managers and Debate Judges 1935-1953 (Box 20)
  - John S. Knight Scholarship Contests 1960-1997, 6 folders (Box 20)
  - John Shively Knight circa 1973 (Box 20)
  - Student Congress 1969-1991, 7 folders (Box 20)
  - Flushing Forensic Team (copy of print) 1935-1936 (Box 20)
  - Individual Events State Tournament 1987/88-1989/90, 3 folders (Box 20)
  - Individual Events -- Pentathlon 1979 (Box 20)
  - Drama/Theatre 1987-1991 (Box 20)
  - Awards and MIFA Offices undated (Box 20)
  - Negatives from the Detroit Free Press 1989 (Box 20)
  - Unidentified, 2 folders (Box 20)
- Activities 1943-2006
  The Activities series is divided into four subseries representing the core student events: Debate; Drama/Theatre; Individual Events; and Legislative Debate. The Debate subseries is further divided into the specific activities of District Debates, State Debates, John S. Knight contests, novice tournaments, and debate leagues/invitational tournaments that are organized chronologically and, in some cases, include topical files. The Drama/Theatre subseries is also divided into chronological and topical files. The Legislative Debate subseries includes chronological and topical files for the spring Discussion Festivals and for the fall Student Congresses held annually in Lansing. The Individual Events subseries likewise contains both chronological and topical files and is further divided into Middle Level materials, District/Regional results, Scripts, State Tournaments, Interpretation Pentathlons, and Original Interpretation Tournaments.
  - Legislative Debate
    - Discussion Festivals (Box 21)
      - Materials for Directors 1974/75-2005/06, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Materials for Regional Festival Directors 1970-2006 (Box 21)
      - Regional Groupings, 1968-2005/06 (Box 21)
      - Objectives (Box 21)
      - List of Participants 1970 (Box 21)
      - Discussion Changes 1979-1980 (Box 21)
      - Discussion Correspondence (Box 21)
      - Regional Results 1973-2004, 29 folders (Box 21)
    - Student Congress
      - Chronological Files 1967-2005
        - 1967-1978, 12 folders (Box 21)
        - 1978-2002, 14 folders (Box 22)
        - 2003-2005, 3 folders (Box 23)
      - Assorted Correspondence 1967-2004, 6 folders (Box 23)
      - Agendas for Congressional Committee Bills 1977-2005 (Box 23)
      - Annual Editions of Rules (Box 23)
      - Annual Legislative Committee Areas 1985-2005 (Box 23)
      - Annual Lists of House Participants 1974-2005 (Box 23)
      - Annual Lists of Senate Participants 1977-2003 (Box 23)
      - Annual Lists of Participants 1974-2005 (Box 23)
      - Annual Participant Lists -- Lobbyists/Organizational Representatives 1974-2005 (Box 23)
      - Brochures, Sponsorship (Box 23)
      - Committee Testimony Schedules 1977-2005 (Box 23)
      - Confirmation Letters 1977-2001 (Box 23)
      - Contracts for Use of State Capitol 1985, 1987 (Box 23)
      - Descriptions of Roles and Responsibilities (Box 23)
      - Executive Branch -- Bills, Orders, Responsibilities, Lists (Box 23)
      - Final Schedules 1969-2005 (Box 23)
      - Legislative Action -- House Bills 1972-2001, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Legislative Action -- Senate Bills 1972-2002, 2 folders (Box 23)
      - Legislative Action -- Joint Bills 1977-2001 (Box 23)
      - Letters to Directors 1986-2005 (Box 23)
      - Letters to Participants 1977-2005 (Box 23)
      - Lists of Candidates for Offices 1981-2001 (Box 23)
      - Lobby Bill Positions (Box 23)
      - Lobbyist Descriptions and Annual Lobby Groups (Box 23)
      - Lobbyist Materials (Box 23)
      - Lodging Correspondence 1971-1984 (Box 23)
      - Michigan House of Representatives -- Rules for Use 1985-2002 (Box 23)
      - Newspaper Articles 1969-1994 (Box 23)
      - Newspaper Layout Instructions (Box 23)
      - Outline of Event, Resolution, Lists of Annual Policy Topics, Summary Lists (Box 23)
      - Parliamentary Rules/Charts (Box 23)
      - Press Participants, Schedules, Press Reporter Description (Box 23)
      - Reports, Revisions, Suggestions 1970-2004 (Box 23)
      - Samples of Participant Packets (Box 23)
      - Samples of Confirmation Packets (Box 23)
  - Drama/Theatre
    - Contests 1969/70-1999/00, 31 folders (Box 24)
    - Contests 2000/01 (Box 25)
    - Contests 2001/02 (Box 25)
    - Contests 2003/04 (Box 25)
    - Contests 2004/05 (Box 25)
    - Contests 2005/06 (Box 25)
    - Contests 2006/07 (Box 25)
    - Annual Lists of Participating Schools 1975/76-2005/06 (Box 25)
    - Articles 1982, 2001 (Box 25)
    - Awards (Box 25)
    - Complaints, Protests, Student Behavior, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - District Configurations 1976/77-2005/06 (Box 25)
    - FAQ Documents/Checklists (Box 25)
    - Financial Information (Box 25)
    - Historical Information (Box 25)
    - Hosting of Festivals; Site Issues (Box 25)
    - Judges, Judging (Box 25)
    - Letters sent to Directors 1982/83-2005/06 (Box 25)
    - Letters to District Hosts 1975/76-2005/06 (Box 25)
    - Letters to Regional Hosts 1985/86-2005/06 (Box 25)
    - Letters to Regional Participants 1985/86-2005/06 (Box 25)
    - Mission Statements, Questionnaire (Box 25)
    - Performance Issues (Box 25)
    - Regional Configurations 1985/86-2005/06 (Box 25)
    - Response to Detroit Free Press Article 1987 (Box 25)
    - Rules, Guidelines, Committee Structure (Box 25)
    - Samples of Contest Structure Packets (Box 25)
    - Samples of District Packets (Box 25)
    - Samples of Regional Host Packets (Box 25)
    - Samples of Packets to Regional Participants (Box 25)
    - School Eligibility/Participation (Box 25)
    - State Drama/Theatre Committee Nominating Ballots; Committee Members 1976/77-2004/05 (Box 25)
    - Teacher of the Year Materials (Box 25)
    - "Thank Yous" (Box 25)
    - Various Awards and Production Summaries (Box 25)
    - Various Proposals (Box 25)
    - Workshop Proposal (Box 25)
  - Debate
    - Assorted Debate Tournaments (Box 26)
    - Big Rapids Invitational 1976 (Box 26)
    - Bound Materials -- Preliminary Series 1946/47-1966/67 (Box 26)
    - Canada Debate Trips 1973-1979, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Detroit Catholic Forensic League 1974-1976 (Box 26)
    - Firestone Tournament (Box 26)
    - Gold Cup Debates (Box 26)
    - Initial Mailing -- Novice Preliminary Tournaments 1976-2002 (Box 26)
    - Invitational Results Forms (Box 26)
    - Invitational Tournament Results 1991/92-1993/94, 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Judge Information -- Novice Preliminary Tournaments 1977-2000 (Box 26)
    - League Chairman Mailings (Box 26)
    - League Constitution Samples (Box 26)
    - League Correspondence 1970s (Box 26)
    - League Correspondence 1980s (Box 26)
    - Leagues -- Nonmember School Letter (Box 26)
    - League Plaques (Box 26)
    - League Plaque Redesign (Box 26)
    - League Protest -- District Eligibility circa 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - League Registrations 1972/73 (Box 26)
    - League Registration Forms (Box 26)
    - League Report 1969/70 (Box 26)
    - League Reports 1974/75-2003/04
      - 1974/75 (Box 26)
      - 1975/76 (Box 26)
      - 1986/87 (Box 26)
      - 1987/88 (Box 26)
      - 1988/89 (Box 26)
      - 1989/90 (Box 26)
      - 1990/91 (Box 26)
      - 1991/92 (Box 26)
      - 1992/93 (Box 26)
      - 1993/94 (Box 26)
      - 1994/95 (Box 26)
      - 1995/96 (Box 26)
      - 1996/97 (Box 26)
      - 1997/98 (Box 27)
      - 1998/99 (Box 27)
      - 1999/00 (Box 27)
      - 2000/01 (Box 27)
      - 2001/02 (Box 27)
      - 2002/03 (Box 27)
      - League Results 2003/04 (Box 27)
    - Lists of Novice Tournament Finalists 1974/75-2003/04 (Box 27)
    - Local League Reports 1971/72 (Box 27)
    - Local League Reports 1973/74 (Box 27)
    - Mackinac Island Debate Tournament 1973 (Box 27)
    - Mailing to Directors -- Novice Preliminary Tournaments 1977/78-2004/05 (Box 27)
    - Mailings to Novice Finals Qualifiers 1976/77-2003/04 (Box 27)
    - Mailing to Participants -- Novice Preliminary Tournaments 1979/80-2004/05 (Box 27)
    - Michigan State University Tournaments 1989, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Novice -- 2 Day Proposal (Box 27)
    - Novice 1999 (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Broken Window 2005 (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Definition Issues 1983 (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Drops (Box 27)
    - Novice Finals Participants -- Tournament Clarifications 1997/98-2001/02 (Box 27)
    - Novice Final Tournament Schematics 1977/78-2002/03 (Box 27)
    - Novice History (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Judge Certification Interpretations 1986 (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Leach Trophy (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Preliminaries Protests 1977/78 (Box 27)
    - Novice Preliminary Tournament Schematics 1975/76-2004/05 (Box 27)
    - Novice Procedures, Rules, and Regulations (Box 27)
    - Novice Sites (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Timing Protests 1976 (Box 27)
    - Novice Tournaments 1970/71-2004/05, 30 folders (Box 27)
    - Novice -- Upper Peninsula Rationale 1975 (Box 27)
    - Novice -- West Bloomfield Issue 1984/85 (Box 27)
    - School Debate Records 1926/27 (Box 27)
    - State Leagues -- Lists of Schools (Box 27)
    - Upper Peninsula Debate Tournament 1963 (Box 27)
    - Wolverine Invitational Debate Tournament 1997 (Box 27)
    - Class A District Reports with Records and At-Large Bids 1974/75 (Box 28)
    - Class B District Reports with Records 1974/75 (Box 28)
    - Class C-D District Reports with Records 1974/75 (Box 28)
    - Class A District Reports and School Debate Records 1976/77 (Box 28)
    - Class B District Reports and School Debate Records 1976/77 (Box 28)
    - Class C-D District Reports and School Debate Records 1976/77 (Box 28)
    - Class B District Reports and School Debate Records 1977/78 (Box 28)
    - District Reports and School Debate Records 1978/79 (Box 28)
    - School Debate Records 1978/79 (Box 28)
    - District Reports and School Debate Records 1979/80 (Box 28)
    - School Debate Records 1979/80 (Box 28)
    - Class A District Reports and School Debate Records 1984/85 (Box 28)
    - Class B District Reports and School Debate Records 1984/85 (Box 28)
    - Class C-D District Reports and School Debate Records 1984/85 (Box 28)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1985/86, 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1985/86, 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1985/86, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1985/86 (Box 29)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1985/86 (Box 29)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1985/86 (Box 29)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1986/87, 6 folders (Box 29)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1986/87, 4 folders (Box 29)